Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Campus Buildings, 189268
  - Washington Square North (Box 202, Box 203, Box 204)
  - Washington Square North - Weehawken Athletic Field (Box 205)
  - Oversize Photos (Box 237)
  - Bobst Library (Box 218, Box 219, Box 220, Box 221, Box 222, Box 223, Box 224, Box 225, Box 226, Box 227)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center for Middle and Near Eastern Studies (Box 228, Box 229)
  - Loeb Student Center (Box 232, Box 233, Box 234, Box 235, Box 236)
  - Main Building (Box 238, Box 239, Box 240)
  - Tisch Hall (Box 241, Box 242, Box 243, Box 244, Box 245)
- Administration
  - Administration, General - Trustees, General (Box 411)
  - Administration, 1980s - President office of the, public occasions (Box 412)
  - Mounted Portraits of Chancellors - Mathews, James M. (Box 413)
  - African-Americans at NYU (Box 414)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., scholars program - Italy International Seminar (Box 415)
  - External Affairs, Office of (Box 416, Box 417)
  - Faculty (Box 418)
  - Finance, Office of - Institutes/Centers (Box 419)
  - NYU Abroad (Box 420, Box 421, Box 422, Box 479)
  - Student Affairs, Office of (Box 423, Box 424, Box 425)
  - University Services (Box 426)
- Alumni
  - Perstare Society Event (Box 471)
  - Photograph of 25th Alumni Day; class of 1932, 1957 (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 2)
- Arts and Science, Faculty of
  - Anthropology - Chemistry faculty (Box 16)
  - Classics - Classics-Archaeology (Box 17)
  - General - FAS classroom scenes (Box 18)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematics, Classes - Courant Institute of Mathematics, Faculty (Box 19)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematics, Faculty (Box 20)
  - Courant Institute of Mathematics, anti-smoke survey - Courant Institute of Mathematics, student demonstration (Box 21)
  - Drama, Green Room Honor Society - Drama, Hall of Fame Playhouse, "Cyprian's Prayer" (Box 22)
  - Drama, Hall of Fame Playhouse, "Dead End," - Unidentified University Heights Theatre Productions (Box 23)
  - Economics - History, Faculty, Maas Essay Contest (Box 24)
  - Journalism - The Writing Center (Box 25)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science (GSAS) (Box 26)
- Class Collection
  - 1843 (Box 316)
  - 1854-1857 (Box 317)
  - 1862-1874 (Box 318)
  - 1866 (Box 319)
  - 1863 - 1879 (Box 320)
  - 1880 - 1884 (Box 321)
  - 1883 (Box 322)
  - 1885 - 1888 (Box 323)
  - 1880 - 1899 (Box 324)
  - 1899 - 1897 (Box 325)
  - 1890 (Box 326)
  - 1900 - 1910 (Box 327)
  - 1911 - 1920 (Box 328)
  - 1921 - 1975 (Box 329)
- Commencement, 248333
  - Commencement, 1925; 248334
  - NYU Alumni (Box 330, Box 331)
  - Alumni Abroad - University Day (Box 332)
  - 1920 - 1923 (Box 333)
  - 1924 - 1928 (Box 334)
  - 1929 - 1934 (Box 335)
  - 1935 - 1938 (Box 336)
  - 1939 - 1949 (Box 337)
  - 1950 - 1952 (Box 338)
  - 1953 - 1957 (Box 339)
  - 1958 - 1963 (Box 340)
  - 1964 - 1965 (Box 341)
  - 1966 - 1967 (Box 342)
  - 1968 - 1970 (Box 343)
  - 1971 (Box 344)
  - 1972 - 1975 (Box 345)
  - 1976 - 1978 (Box 346)
  - 1979 - 1981 (Box 347)
  - 1982 - 1983 (Box 348)
  - 1984 - 1985 (Box 349)
  - 1985 - 1987 (Box 350)
  - 1988 - 1990s (Box 351)
  - 1991 - 1997 (Box 352)
  - 1995 - 2001 (Box 353)
  - Miscellaneous - Trustees (Box 354)
  - Glass plate negatives, 1926 (Box Shared University Archives 019)
- Dentistry, College of/Dental Center, 248346
  - NY College of Dentistry, 1925; 248347
    - NY College of Dentistry 1 -- Negative, 1925; 248348 (Item 12)
    - NY College of Dentistry 2 -- Negative, 1925; 248349 (Item 13)
  - 1st Ave old building - NY College of Dentistry (Box 53)
  - Classes - Contacts (Box 54)
  - Contacts - Examinations (Box 55)
  - Examinations - Laboratory, Anatomy (Box 56)
  - Laboratories and Research - NYCD Medals (Box 57)
  - Franklin J. Miller Collection - Site prior to construction (Box 58)
  - Special Events - White Coat Ceremony (Box 59)
  - Special Events, general - Students, class photos (Box 60)
  - TV Studio - New Dental Center (Box 61)
  - 19th Century Tools - Misc. Dental Photos (Box 477)
- Engineering, School of
  - Aeronautical -Chart Organization (Box 89)
  - Chemical - Geology (Box 90)
  - Geophysics - Promotional material (Box 91)
  - Prosthetic Devices - Surveying (Box 92)
  - Research Division - Negatives #1-4000 (Box 93)
  - Research Division - Negatives #4001-5199 (Box 94)
  - Research Division - Negatives #5200-7500 (Box 95)
  - Bulletin Images (Box 96, Box 97)
- Fine Arts, College of/School of Architecture and Allied Science
  - Aerial Views - Doorways and Windows (Box 98)
  - Chan Conservation Center - Laboratory (Box 99)
  - Lawrence J. Majewski Papers - Slide room (Box 100)
- Gallatin School of Individualized Study
  - Artists - Oscar Dystel Fellowship (Box 101)
  - Special Events (Box 102)
  - Classroom Scenes - Special Events (Box 103)
- Individual Collections
  - Richards, John, circa 1880s-1890s, 1945 (Box Individual Collections 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Glass plate images of Washington Square (including University Building). Also includes a glass plate taken by D.W. Hering of Andrew H. Green plaque. Purchased from John Richards in 1945.
  - Arthur, James, clock and watch collection (Box 376)
  - Bouton, Archibald (Box 377, Box 378)
  - Bennett, James Gordon - Sihler, Henry (Box 379)
  - Newsom, Carol (Box 380, Box 381)
  - Still, Bayrd; Otness, Robert (Box 382)
  - Brademas, John O. (from the US House of Representatives) (Box 383)
  - Edwards, Henry Clay (Box 384)
  - Bill, Charles A. (Box 385)
  - Jewish Culture Foundation (Box 386)
- Law, School of
  - Alumni Events, 2002-2006 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
  - Class of 1934 Poster (Box 63)
  - 130 MacDougal - Alumni (Box 104)
  - Alumni (Box 105, Box 106, Box 107, Box 108, Box 109, Box 111, Box 112, Box 110)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend - Americorps (Box 113)
  - Annual Survey - Black Allied Law Students (Box 114)
  - BLAPA - Centerfold (Box 115)
  - Chelsea Tenant Cleaning and Renovation - Classes (Box 116)
  - Clinic Students - Community Service Award (Box 117)
  - Conferences - Convocation (Box 118)
  - Convocation (Box 119, Box 120)
  - Copyright Society - Dean's Day (Box 121)
  - Dean's Day - Entertainment Art (Box 122)
  - Environmental Law Journal - Faculty (Box 123)
  - Faculty (Box 124)
  - Faculty and Students - Family Court (Box 125)
  - Flag - IJA (Box 126)
  - IJA - Jacob Javits Convention Center (Box 127)
  - James Madison Lectures - Journals (Box 128)
  - Katz, George A. Torch of Learning Award - La Pietra Conferences (Box 129)
  - La Pietra - Law and Accounting Conference (Box 130)
  - Law and Development in Asia - Legal Aid Society (Box 131)
  - Library - Members of the Class of 1951 (Box 132)
  - Class of 1956 - Class of 1976 (Box 133)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 134, Box 135)
  - Mock Class - NYU Newsletter (Box 136)
  - OCCP - ProBono Poster (Box 137)
  - Public Interest Law Foundation - Publications (Box 138)
  - Promotional Material - Symposium on the Rights of Peoplef (Box 139)
  - Role of Presidents Council - Rubin Scholars (Box 140)
  - Class Roll - Root Tilden (Box 141)
  - Root Tilden (Box 142, Box 143, Box 144)
  - Russian Professors Cocktail - Special Events (Box 145)
  - Special Events (Box 146, Box 147, Box 149, Box 148, Box 150, Box 151)
  - Spring Fling - Student Portraits (Box 152)
  - Students (Box 153)
  - Symposium - Urban Law Clinic (Box 154)
  - Urban Research Forum - Harold Weill Medal (Box 155)
  - Weinfeld - Zenger (Box 156)
  - Contact (Box 157, Box 158)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives (Box 159)
- Libraries
  - Depository Library Decal - Libraries moved into Bobst (Box 173)
  - NYU Archives - Wagner Labor Archives (Box 174)
- Medicine, School of, 248604
  - Senior Class -- Negative, 1903; 248605
  - Images of Healing - Aerial Views (Box 160)
  - Aerial Views - Site prior to construction (Box 161)
  - Construction - Exteriors (Box 162)
  - Faculty - Patients (Box 163)
  - Personnel - Veterinary College (Box 164)
  - Rehabilitation, Center for (Box 165)
  - Contacts (Box 166, Box 167)
  - Construction (Box 168, Box 169)
- Military, 248356
  - Cannon -- Negative, 1921; 248357 (Item 25)
  - Cannon, Ft #8 -- Negative, 1918; 248358 (Item 26)
  - Gun Group at Battery Hill -- Negative, 1925; 248384 (Item 50)
  - World War I (Box 387, Box 388, Box 389)
  - World War II (Box 390, Box 391, Box 392)
  - ROTC (Box 393)
  - World War II, Heights Memorial Collection (Box 394, Box 395, Box 396, Box 397)
- Professional Studies, School of
  - American Language Institute - Classes/Students & Professors (Box 51)
  - Cooper Square - Special Events (Box 52)
- Social Work, Graduate School of
  - Classes - Contacts (Box 171)
  - Exteriors - Special Events (Box 172)
- Unprocessed Material Transferred from RG 3.0.10, 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  These two boxes were transferred from RG 3.0.10 on 11/14/2019 after it was determined they were most likely photographs used in an NYU publication, including portraits of professors, students in various NYU locations (Florence, London, etc) from the 1990s.
  - Associations of University Architects at NYU - NYU Calendar Book (Box 398)
  - CAS Yearbook Photographs (Box 399)
  - Book and Engravers Plates (Box 400)
  - NYU Icons (Box 401, Box 402, Box 403, Box 405)
  - Surveyor's Maps and Drawings (Box 404)
  - Bobst Exhibit (Box 406)
  - NYC and Philadelphia Colonial Scenes and Maps (Box 407)
  - Alumni Federation (Box 408, Box 409, Box 410)
  - Freedom's World Exhibition (Box 431)
- Special Collections
  - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown, 1925; 248330
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 1 -- Negative, 1925; 248331 (Item 1)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 2 -- Negative, 1925; 248332 (Item 2)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 3 -- Negative, 1925; 248335 (Item 3)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 4 -- Negative, 1925; 248336 (Item 4)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 5 -- Negative, 1925; 248337 (Item 5)
    - General Pershing and Chancellor Brown 6 -- Negative, 1925; 248338 (Item 6)
  - Founders Day, 90th Anniversary, 1921; 248339
    - Founders Day, 90th Anniversary 1 -- Negative, 1921; 248340 (Item 7)
    - Founders Day, 90th Anniversary 2 -- Negative, 1921; 248341 (Item 8)
  - Marshall Foch -- Negative, 1921; 248373 (Item 40)
  - 6th Annual Memorial Service - Heights Alumni Dinner (Box 355)
  - American Association of University Presidents - Baroness Zerilli (Box 356)
  - Beauty Pageant - Chancellor's Service Award (Box 357)
  - Chancellor's Service Award - Conference, various (Box 358)
  - Commercial Shoot - Courant Institute (Box 359)
  - Dean's Day - For Whom the Bell Tolls (Box 360)
  - Founders Day - Global Initiative Trip (Box 361)
  - Global Initiative Trip - International Festival (Box 362)
  - Hertsberg Lecture - Lecture, Phelps (Box 363)
  - Lecture, Reilly - Meeting, Humanities Council (Box 364)
  - Mortgage - One to One (Box 365)
  - Parents Day - Silverstein Scholarships (Box 366)
  - Royal Shakespeare Company at NYU - Visit, Foreign Dignitaries (Box 367)
  - Visit, Foreign Dignitaries - Typhoid Inoculation (Box 368)
  - Miscellaneous 1980s events (Box 369, Box 370, Box 371, Box 372, Box 373)
  - Miscellaneous 1990s events - Dean Daley (Box 374)
  - Miscellaneous 2000s events (Box 375)
- Special Events, 248329
  - Baseball Team, 1931 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Administration - Baseball (Box 258, Box 259, Box 260, Box 261)
  - Basketball (Box 262, Box 263, Box 264, Box 265, Box 266, Box 267, Box 268, Box 269)
  - Ballroom Dancing - Fencing, First Aid (Box 270, Box 271, Box 272)
  - Basketball Team, 1909 (Box Shared University Archives 004, Folder 13)
  - Football (Box 273, Box 274)
  - Golf - Promotional Material (Box 275)
  - Racquetball - Soccer (Box 276)
  - Soccer (Box 277)
  - Sports Clinic - Swimming (Box 278, Box 279)
  - Table Tennis - Tennis (Box 280)
  - Track and Field (Box 281, Box 282, Box 283)
  - Trophy - Weehawken Athletic Field (Box 284)
  - Oversized and Framed Photos (Box 285)
- Sports/Athletics
  - Arts and Crafts - Buildings, interiors (Box 478)
  - Children - Classes (Box 64)
  - Classes (Box 65)
  - Clinic for Learning - HEOP (Box 66)
  - Home Economics - Musical Therapy (Box 67)
  - Nursing - Nutrition (Box 68)
  - Occupational Safety - Rehabilitation (Box 69)
  - Sculpture - Telecommunications (Box 70)
  - Theatre, Educational, Miscellaneous prints - Summer Musical Theatre (Box 71)
  - Theatre, Educational, "In a Minor Key" - "Don Pasquale" (Box 72)
  - Theatre, Educational, "Wonderful Town" - "Cabaret" (Box 73)
  - Physical Education, Camp, Lake Sebago (Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Box 77, Box 78, Box 79, Box 80, Box 81, Box 82, Box 83)
  - Puerto Rican Teachers - United Nations Institute (Box 84)
  - Special Events (Box 85)
  - Summer School (Box 86)
  - Class Scenes - Contacts (Box 87)
  - Contacts (Box 88)
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development, 248351
  - Buildings - NIchols Hall (Box 27)
  - Nichols Hall, Construction - NIchols Hall, Exteriors (Box 28)
  - Nichols and Merril Hall - Tisch Hall (Box 29)
  - Administration - Trial Evidence, Nichols building violation (Box 30)
  - Classes (Box 31)
  - Commencement - Trial evidence, Nichols building violation (Box 32)
  - BPA/GBA Faculty Contracts - Faculty teaching (Box 33)
  - Library - Symposia (Box 34)
  - Special Events, general (Box 35)
  - Special Events, general - 1980s+1990s negatives (Box 36)
  - Special Events, 50th Anniversary - Special Events, Taggert, Dean, Memorial Service (Box 37)
- Stern School of Business (Graduate)
  - Administration meeting - Classes and students (Box 38)
  - Classes and students - Classroom Blueprint (Box 39)
  - Clubs - Japan Center (Box 40)
  - Manhattanville, Campus - Seminar Classes (Box 41)
  - Special events, general (Box 42)
  - Special events, general (Box 43)
  - Special events, Class of 1914 dinner - Special Events, Reception in honor of Theodore R. Racoosin (Box 44)
  - Contacts: Special events - Negatives, BPA Yearbook (Box 45)
  - Contacts: Special events - Leather Bound Scrapbooks donated by Dean Abraham L. Gitlow (Box 46)
  - Tisch Hall Groundbreaking Ceremony (Box 47)
  - Special Events Leather Bound Scrapbooks - The Eleventh Charles C. Moskowitz Lecture (Box 48)
  - Special Events Leather Bound Scrapbooks - Tisch Hall Dedication (Box 49)
  - Retailing, School of (Box 170)
- Stern School of Business (Undergraduate)
  - Accounting Club - Bun (Box 286)
  - Campus Scenes (Box 287, Box 288, Box 289, Box 290, Box 291, Box 292)
  - Cane Rush - College Bowl (Box 293)
  - Colonnade Board - Dormitories (Box 294)
  - Dramatic Society - Eucleian Literary Society (Box 295)
  - Fall Festival - Freshmen (Box 296)
  - Fraternities (Box 297, Box 298)
  - Pi Lambda Theta (Box 299)
  - Gay Organizations/Protests, 1970; 166863 (Box 300)
    - Gay Pride Parade - Central Park, 1970; wsp_gv_8_4_01; 166864; color (photograph), 4 x 4 inches (Box 300)
  - Gavel Club - Guitar Contest (Box 300)
  - Ice Skating - LUCHA (Box 301)
  - Management Club - Pit Day (Box 302)
  - Press Club - Student Portraits (Box 303)
  - Student Portraits (Box 304, Box 305)
  - Protests (Box 306, Box 307, Box 308, Box 309, Box 310, Box 311)
  - Publications, staff - Sororities (Box 312)
  - Sororities - Student Pranks (Box 313)
  - Students Union Office - Wall Street Organization (Box 314)
  - Students in WSP - Youth Leadership Training Program (Box 315)
- Student Life
  - Advisement - Classroom Scenes (Box 1)
  - Communication Arts - Dressing Room (Box 2)
  - Dance Classes (Box 3)
  - Dance performances (Box 4)
  - Dance contacts (Box 5)
  - Dean's office - Dramatic writing (Box 6)
  - Drama-contact prints (Box 7)
  - Drama performances - Film Faculty (Box 8)
  - Film Faculty - Future Filmmakers Program (Box 9)
  - Film and TV contacts (Box 10)
  - Film and Television program - Graduate Acting Program Workshops (Box 11)
  - Make-up class - Movie stills (Box 12)
  - Movement class - Singing (Box 13)
  - Special events (Box 14)
  - Contacts-Stage Design - Theatre Design (Box 15)
- Tisch School of the Arts
  - Nichols Hall -- Negative, 1928; 248354 (Item 22)
  - Philosophy Hall -- Negative, 1922; 248359 (Item 27)
  - Private Houses, Kimball -- Negative, 1924; 248362 (Item 30)
  - Brown House -- Negative, 1925; 248360 (Item 28)
  - University College from River -- Negative, 1921; 248361 (Item 29)
  - Electrolier at Library -- Negative, 1922; 248363 (Item 31)
  - Gould Library Doors, 248364
    - Gould Library Doors 1 -- Negative, 1921; 248370 (Item 33)
    - Gould Library Doors 2 -- Negative, 1921; 248371 (Item 38)
    - Gould Library Doors 3 -- Negative, undated; 248382 (Item 48)
  - Graduate Hall, 248598
    - Graduate Hall -- Negative, 1925; 248355 (Item 24)
    - Graduate Hall -- Negative, 1926; 248366 (Item 35)
  - Biological Laboratories -- Negative, 1924; 248365 (Item 34)
  - Hall of Philosophy -- Negative, 1926; 248367 (Item 36)
  - University Heights Campus Bridge -- Negative, 1926; 248372 (Item 39)
  - Eastman Pyrometal Tank, 248374
    - Eastman Pyrometal Tank 1 -- Negative, 1926; 248387 (Item 41)
    - Eastman Pyrometal Tank 2 -- Negative, 1928; 248388 (Item 53)
  - Fountain -- Negative, 1921; 248375 (Item 42)
  - Lipton Flag Mast -- Negative, 1925; 248377 (Item 44)
  - Gould Memorial Library, 248378
    - Gould Memorial Library 1 -- Negative, undated; 248379 (Item 45)
    - Gould Memorial Library 2 -- Negative, undated; 248380 (Item 46)
    - Gould Memorial Library 3 -- Negative, undated; 248381 (Item 47)
  - Gould Hall -- Negative, undated; 248383 (Item 49)
  - University Heights Neighborhood -- Negative, 1926; 248385 (Item 51)
  - University Heights Neighborhood from Hall of Fame -- Negative, 1926; 248386 (Item 52)
  - Aerial View of University Heights Campus and Neighborhood 1 -- Negative, 1938; 248601
  - Aerial View of University Heights Campus and Neighborhood 2 -- Negative, undated; 248602
  - Power House -- Negative, 1926; 248390 (Item 55)
  - South Hall, 248391
    - South Hall 1 -- Negative, 1926; 248392 (Item 56)
    - South Hall 2 -- Negative, 1926; 248393 (Item 57)
  - New Grandstand -- Negative, 1925; 248396 (Item 61)
  - General Views - unidentified (Box 427)
  - Gould Library (Box 428)
  - Oversized - Gould Student Center (Box 429)
  - Dean Thorndike Saville - General Views (Box 430)
  - General Views (Box 432, Box 434)
  - Aerial views (Box 433, Box 435)
  - Aerospace laboratory - Biology Laboratories (Box 436)
  - Bliss Engineering Laboratory - Engineering WW II Photo Album (Box 437)
  - Engineering - Gould Hall of Technology (Box 438)
  - Gould Library, Exteriors - Gould Library, Stanford White Memorial Doors (Box 476)
  - Gould Library interiors (Box 439)
  - Gould Library, exteriors - Gould House (Box 440)
  - Gould Student Center (Box 441)
  - Green Laboratory - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics (Box 442)
  - Gymnasium (Box 443)
  - Hall of Fame (Box 444)
  - Hall of Fame (Box 445, Box 446, Box 447, Box 448, Box 449)
  - Havermeyer Hall of Chemistry - Knoop Sculpture (Box 450)
  - Laboratories - Machinery (Box 451)
  - Mali Estate (Box 452)
  - Neighborhood - Negatives (Box 453)
  - Nichols Building (Box 454)
  - Plans - Silver Residence Hall (Box 455)
  - Sonic Boom Lab - YMCA (Box 456)
  - Schwab House and Estate (Box 457)
  - World War II Engineering album (Box 458)
- University Heights, 248353
  - Artist's renderings - Exteriors (Box 251, Box 252, Box 253)
- Vanderbilt Hall/Law School
  - Special Events - Students (Box 50)
- Wagner Graduate School of Public Service
  - Construction site - Sculpture (Box 254, Box 255, Box 256, Box 257)
- Weinstein Center for Student Living
  - Landmark Buildings (Box 459)
  - Aerial views of NYC - Atomic Bomb Drill (Box 460)
  - Barnes & Noble - City Skylines (Box 461)
  - City Scenes (Box 462, Box 463)
  - Clinton Court - Garment District (Box 464)
  - Goulandris Museum - Manhattan street scenes (Box 465)
  - Map of NYC - NY Police (Box 466)
  - NYPL - Presidents (Box 467)
  - Radio City Music Hall - Soho (Box 468)
  - South Church - Telephones (Box 469)
  - Theatre District - Yellow Brick Road (Box 470)
- Non-NYU Subjects
  - Senior Ball, 1934 (Box Shared University Archives 091, Folder 8)
  - Illustrations (Box 472)
  - Digital photos on physical media (Box 474)
  - Separated photos, RG 4.2, RG 9.7 (Box 475)
  - Group photos at an awards ceremony, undated (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of building labeled "To Julius Silver with gratitude and appreciation from the staff of the Institute", undated (Box Shared University Archives 042, Folder 4)
  - Photos pulled for Oliva exhibit (Box 475)
- Miscellaneous
  - Albert Sheppard -- Negative, undated; 248343 (Item 9)
  - E.G. Hesser -- Negative, undated; 248344 (Item 10)
  - Alvin Busse -- Negative, undated; 248345 (Item 11)
  - Herbert M. Schiffer -- Negative, undated; 248600
  - Charles Pieper -- Negative, undated; 248603
- Series VII: Portrait Files (unpublished), 248342
  - College Insignia on Large Fountain at Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1921; 248369 (Item 37)
  - Fountain at Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1921; 248599
  - Fountain at Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1922; 248376 (Item 43)
  - Looking Across Palisades from Hall of Fame - Exteriors -- Negative, 1926; 248389 (Item 54)
  - Hall of Fame, Sedgwick Avenue - Exteriors -- Negative, 1928; 248394 (Item 58)
  - Hall of Fame -- Negative, 1928; 248395 (Item 59)
  - Hall of Fame Bust Unveiling Ceremony, 1930 (Box Shared University Archives 004)
- Series XII: Hall of Fame (unpublished), 248368
  - Negative Used to Print Book on School of Science Labs -- Negative, 1925; 248398 (Item 32)
  - Untitled -- Negative, 1915; 248399 (Item 60)
- Series XIII: Untitled? (unpublished), 248397
  - Photographs of Professors, Students, and NYU Locations in Other Countries, 1990s (Box 480, Box 481)